so i've seen a lot about pushing p can
you solve for p yeah we can do this so
oliver is pushing p p is equal to the
sum from one to three of one over n
minus two so we take n equals one we add
to it whatever n equals two and then we
add to whatever n equals 3 and we stop
because there's a 3 on top of this so p
is going to be equal to the sum of these
three we're going to do 1 over n minus 2
we're going to plug in 1 for the n plus
1 minus 2 plug in 2 for the n so it's 2
minus 2 and plugging 3 for the n it's 3
minus 2. bring down the p and one over
one minus two gives us one over negative
one one over two minus two gives us one
over zero and one over three minus two
gives us one over one one over negative
one is negative one so negative one plus
one is zero so these cancel each other
out so we're left with p is equal to one
over zero and that is undefined and
that's the reason why nobody can explain
to me what pushing p means that's it i'm
done thank you